export default [
    {
        bg: "#8FD4EB",
        category: "Category 1",
        subCategories: [
            {question: "Question 1?", answer: "This is the answer for the question one"}, 
            {question: "Question 2?", answer: "This is the answer for the question two"}
        ]
    },
    {
        bg: "#3293B4",
        category: "Category 2",
        subCategories: [
            {question: "Question 3?", answer: "This is the answer for the question three"}, 
            {question: "Question 4?", answer: "This is the answer for the question four"}
        ]
    },
    {
        bg: "#263A5F",
        category: "Category 3",
        subCategories: [
            {question: "Question 5?", answer: "This is the answer for the question five"}, 
            {question: "Question 6?", answer: "This is the answer for the question six"}
        ]
    },
    {
        bg: "#B0AAAC",
        category: "Category 4",
        subCategories: [
            {question: "Question 7?", answer: "This is the answer for the question seven"}, 
            {question: "Question 8?", answer: "This is the answer for the question eight"}
        ]
    },
    {
        bg: "#EBD325",
        category: "Category 5",
        subCategories: [
            {question: "Question 9?", answer: "This is the answer for the question nine"}, 
            {question: "Question 10?", answer: "This is the answer for the question ten"}
        ]
    }
]